DARIAN YANE

Mar del Plata, Argentina · (+54) 11-5311-7020
www.darianyane.com - yanedarian.dev@gmail.com
github.com/DarianYane - # PYTHON # DJANGO # BACKEND



Junior Python Developer, MBA and Bachelor's Degree in Economics.

WHY SHOULD YOU HIRE ME?

I WILL BE PRODUCTIVE FROM DAY ONE!

My knowledge of **Python, Django, Bootstrap**, Statistics, Economics and Finance, added to my extensive work experience in all types of companies and teams, makes my incorporation to any company or team extremely fluid and effective. In addition, I can work perfectly well in a group or autonomously.

EDUCATION

2022

PYTHON, CODERHOUSE

Python course where you learn to program with functions, POO, CBV and Django.



2020

MASTER'S DEGREE IN BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION (MBA), UADE

Distinction: MAGNA CUM LAUDE

Average: 8,68 (2nd best course average)

2011

BACHELOR'S DEGREE IN ECONOMICS, UBA

SKILLS

PROGRAMMING	PYTHON, Solidity
FRAMEWORKS	DJANGO, BOOTSTRAP
DATA PROCESSING	SQL, Pandas, Numpy
DATA VISUALIZATION	Matplotlib
WEB DEVELOPMENT	CSS, HTML
OTHERS	GIT, EXCEL (with MACROS), POWER
	QUERY, POWER BI



LANGUAGES

ADVANCED ENGLISH, ADVANCED PORTUGUESE, NATIVE SPANISH

PROJECTS

MY PORTFOLIO

Project developed in Django to get my first job. It includes my projects, an "About me" section, and a contact form.

NUTRIPLAN

Nutriplan allows you to generate personalized diets quickly. In addition, its randomized food selection system prevents the person from abandoning the diet because it is monotonous. A new diet can be generated every week!

FAST READING

This application allows you to format a text to make it faster to read. This is achieved by giving "bold" formatting to the first 2 letters of each word.

TRAVEL BLOG

Final project of the Python course at Coderhouse. It includes a CRUD and a user management system.

EXPERIENCE

12/2022 - PRESENT

TUTOR IN PYTHON COURSE, CODERHOUSE

• Pre-delivery correction

09/2021 - 01/2023

INVESTMENT ANALYST/EDITOR, INVERSOR GLOBAL

- Traditional stock market investments and cryptocurrencies
- Research Analyst
- Newsletters, reports, webinars, daily interactive streams, YouTube live-streams, and video content for social media.

08/2022 - 10/2022

PROFESSOR "CRYPTOCURRENCIES AND FINTECH", CODERHOUSE

- 2 weekly video calls and additional classes for 5 weeks.
- 100 students.

01/2019 - 08/2020

TEAM LEADER ACCOUNTS PAYABLE (AP), AES SERVICIOS AMÉRICA

- Accounting review of invoices from suppliers in Chile and Argentina
- Payment proposal review
- Team coordination: 8 people

You can see the rest of my professional experience at www.linkedin.com/in/darian-yane/

OTHER KNOWLEDGE AND INTERESTS

Economics, Finance, Investments, Statistics, Sports, Science, Technology, Innovation, Education, Blockchain.

AWARDS

- 1st Place Tournament "ACBSP Company Game", 2019, Company Game.
- Member of the <u>Argentine Team that participated in the 9th Southern Cone Olympiad</u>, 1998, Argentine Mathematical Olympiad (OMA).
- National Mention in the 13th Argentine Mathematical Olympiad, 1996, Argentine Mathematical Olympiad (OMA).

NEXT STEPS

2023

- DATA SCIENSE COURSE
- CONTINUE IMPROVING MY **ENGLISH**

2024

- MACHINE LEARNING
- ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE